Oh! Nice sound!
Nice shot!
Wow!
Ew, so cute!
Too cute for words.
Hello!
I'm Mr. Sasaki.
I'm Ayaka Takamoto.
Today we're here at Alpen Tokyo in Shinjuku.
You can see a little bit more about us here.
We've been practicing golf for a while.
So Kumi-chan got her clubs.
That's right.
She has clubs.
So today we wanted to get our golf clubs together.
Here we are.
We're here.
I think it's very important to have your own animals.
I really do.
I also want to buy some cute clothes today.
Oh, I want one.
I want to wear it.
I want to wear cute clothes.
Yes, that's right.
I came here to look for them.
I'd like to share with you how it went.
Here she is.
This is the person who will guide us today. Please.
Pleased to meet you. My name is Sasaki, a fitter at Alpine Tokyo Golf Five Flags Zipster Shinjuku.
Mr. Sasaki, nice to meet you.Mr. Sasaki, nice to meet you.
How long have you been with us?
I've been doing this for about 3 months.
What are you doing with your clubs now?
I rent clubs.
I have a beginner's set right here.
I have a lot of clubs.
I don't really know the difference yet.
I'll leave it to you.
I look forward to working with you.
Let's do it.
Yes, please.
As planned.
Wow!
Yes.
I'm so excited.
Is that okay?
The iron is just an oven that can be shaved down a bit.
That's right.
It's a good learning experience.
That's good.
Let's hit a little bit of the pull that we've been working on.
Yes.
Wow!
Oh! Good!
Nice sound!
Nice show!
You're good!
What? Really?
Three months old? That's how long it's been since I've seen you. Three months? That's how long it's been?
Yes, about three months.
Oh, good.
Oh, I got it straight.
Beautiful.
The distance is good.
From what I can see...
I'm fine with a beginner's set.
But I think it's better to have a long-lasting image
I think it's better for you to have a long-lasting image.
That's not quite right.
I understand.
Teccio.
Yes, Tecsio.
It's called a core.
It's very wide.
When it hits, it's resistant to miss-hit.
Wow, that makes me happy.
That's great.
Oh, yeah, that's good, that's good, that's a nice shot
Good, good, good, yes, not even close
Nice shot, nice shot
It's light, it's light, it feels like it hits something, it felt good.
That's important, too, especially for those who actually use it.
I think it would be good if you could tell us how it feels, as a sensation.
So I would like to ask you to try a longer driver.
I understand.
First of all, as I mentioned before, we are talking about a weight similar to the beginner's set.
Yes, sir.
Oh! Ooh.
Mm-hmm. Mm-hmm.
Wow.
Pretty solid head speed.
Yes, sir.
Touchable, even among beginners
Oh, wow.
Well, since we're here...
I'll take the iron red sexio.
Yes, sir.
Wow, it sounds great. The sound is totally different. It's going the distance.
It's true.
Oh, wow.
It's coming out really well. It's max short.
Now, XXIO and the old bedroom yoke ram. It's close to the gun, so I'm having him shoot it.
Trust 1m only.
The sound is different, too. The sound is different. The feel was different too.
This is the easiest to take.
Eh, what do you think?
I feel like this and this.
So, a beginner's set is fine,
A beginner's set can be replaced as soon as you make some progress.
So, I think it would be better to start with a club that can be used from beginner to intermediate level.
I thought it would be a good idea to start with a club that can be used from the beginner level to the intermediate level.
I also thought that it would be good to make clubs that can be used from beginner to intermediate level from the beginning.
Really?
Yes, that's right. I've had people buy a beginner's set and come back to me after a month or so saying it's not good enough.
I think that in the long run, it is definitely better to buy this set.
In the long run, this one is definitely better.
It is better to get used to it from the beginning. I thought it would be better to get used to it from the beginning.
I will probably improve quickly, so I think it's the way I feel about swinging now.
I don't have enough.
Oh, Kun-chan.
You're so crazy, Kun-chan.
Well, that's all right.
I'm just going to say it now.
Kun-chan's semi-chan.
Is it me?
It feels heavier than mine.
This is so much heavier.
Well then, let's try Mike's.
I'm going to try a little zection, too.
I've been working on my zections.
Wow!
It's totally different.
In the mic.
Oh, good.
Ooh.
Nice shot.
Good, good.
It feels like it's easy to hit the core
Yes, sir.
That's great.That's great.
I knew that using a logo with a higher level of functionality was a good idea.
I can feel it there.
Yeah, it's great.
And since you're here for the driver, too, I'd like to take a look at it.
Oh, thank you very much.
Wow! The sound is so good! What the hell! It's totally different!
Would you like that one?
It's in there, don't hear the difference.
Oh! Wow!
I just changed the saft hardness.
Wow! I see!
I had them use a softer shaft.
Beginners swing the softest women's shaft
The beginners swing the softest women's shafts.
But after a year of playing, their swing speed is quite fast.
If you want to swing hard, it is better to make it a little stiffer.
Oh! Kamu-kun! Did you buy it?
Thank you very much!
If you're a beginner putter, or if you prefer a gentler putter, you can use a large putter like this one.
Heh.
Big putter type.
Looks like a cat.
Looks like an ogre!
Looks like an ogre.
If you open it wide, there are two types of putters like this.
This one is called a metal mold.
This one is thinner, so if you hit the core, you hit it straight, but if you miss the core, like now, you'll lose.
But if you miss the core and hit it here, like now, you'll lose.
The image of the base opening up. The image of the base opening
And when it hits this side, the image of the base closing comes out quite a bit.
So it is better to have a thicker base.
Whether this side hits the bare foot or the heel
So if this side hits the bare foot or the heel, the base will be straight as much as possible.
So, I'm going to make it straight as much as possible.
I'm going to hit it.
Ah!
Oh!
So close! So close!
Now, pull it back, and then pop it here.
Just pull it like you're popping it.
Don't pull so far back.
Let it run forward a little bit gently.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, forward.
That's right.
Now you just jumped here.
Yes, yes, yes.
I'm in!
Good!
It's in.
Have a good day.
Oh!
Aaah!
Wow!
Have a good day.
Yes, nice!
Ooh! I'm in. Oh! I'm in.
You're good.
Nice!
But it's easy to hit. It's so easy to hit.
It's easy to hit.
Yes, sir.
You've got the paperwork to say you're done, like this.
I see, but do you putt all the balls?
I see.
Certainly.
When you think about all the balls, there's hardly any putters.
Wow.
Putters are important.
It's the most important.
Next, I'd like to go to the wear.
So cute!
Already so cute!
Really cute!
I've always wanted to wear golf wear, because I only wear it when I play golf.
That's really true.
I just caught a glimpse of it over there.
Let's go.
Sure, of course.
Around here.
Wait, Kumichan!
We're in front of Gomery.
You passed my camera, Kumichan.
I thought...
He's so cute.
She likes it around here. I like it... around here.
And it's sky blue.
The collar is so cute!
One collar
So cute!
This is so cute!
Let's try it on when you wear it!
So cute!
This is so cute!
I think I like Reiju a lot.
This top looks good on her.
I think it looks good with this one too.
It doesn't have to be a set-up.
It's so cute.
I'm obsessed with golf wear.
I'll put this in the basket.
Yes, please.
I'm off.
I'm off. I'm off.
I'm going.
Oh!
Ta-da!
So cute! It's super cute.
Isn't it super cute?
Oh, my God.
It's so cute!Oh, man.
It really looks good on you.
And it's the perfect size.
It's a perfect size.
This knit is for the coming season.
It's the coming season for us, right?
That's right.
The season is just around the corner!
This is so great!
I love it! I love it!
Let's see the beige skirt version!
I'll show you the beige skirt version.
So cute!
That's cute.
I like that one too.
It's high-waisted, so I'd wear it like this.
If I had one of these, I could easily match it to many different rooms.
It can also be worn in the summer, I'm sure.
Next, Kumi...
I'll be next.
Okay, what do you want me to say?
Okay, okay...
Here we go.
Here you go.
There you go.
Oh!
This one's cute, too.
So cute!
Too cute for words. Maybe I'll put it in a ponytail. Too cute for words. Maybe I'll put it in a ponytail now.
It's so cute!
The fleece is so cute and knit.
It's super cute.
It looks too good on you.
I'll see you in a change of clothes.
I'll see you later.
I'll be waiting.
You're all changed.
I'm going.
I'll wait for you.
Wow, nice girl.
She's cute.
It's a little bit, you know, really overflowing with the good-girl vibe.
This skirt is really nice.
That skirt's so versatile. I still like the hittrick art. Here.
It's so cute in the back.
No, it's really beautiful.
The silhouette is so...
The silhouette's really beautiful.
It's nice.
So, it was a fashion show.
It was a fashion show
Cute, cute
I knew this snowboarding type
Yes, so you did a lot of shopping
Yes, lots and lots of things
So many things! Various
It was super fun.
It was a lot of fun!
We're hoping to try a short course next time.
I'll send you a video of that too.
I'll show you what we bought at that time.
Yes, please look forward to it!
What I liked about this video is that
Please subscribe to our channel, give us a high rating and comment!
Bye bye!